

<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<generator>Kungfu Software</generator>
		<title>Kungfu Software</title>
		<link>http://www.kungfusoftware.net</link>
		<description>A simple blog to describe the company's whole journey.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<webMaster>admin@kungfusoftware.net</webMaster>
		<copyright>2015</copyright>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 12:17:05 GMT</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 12:17:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		
			<item>
	<title>AEM in a nut shell</title>
	<link>http://www.kungfusoftware.net/posts/aem-in-a-nut-shell</link>
	<guid>/posts/aem-in-a-nut-shell</guid>
	
	<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<description>AEM Adobe Strategy Cloud technology: Marketing Cloud Services AEM Adobe Target Adobe Analytics Adobe Data Workbench Adobe Campaign Adobe Social Adobe Media Optimizer Creative Cloud Services Photoshop Dreamweaver flash xxx AEM Main Components Adobe Web Content Management Adobe Content Repository Extreme (CRX) Adobe JCR Connectors DAM Adobe Advanced Collaboration, workflow...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>So much sutff now in hybris 5.7</title>
	<link>http://www.kungfusoftware.net/posts/so-much-stuff-in-hybris5702</link>
	<guid>/posts/so-much-stuff-in-hybris5702</guid>
	
	<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<description>Let’s have a look what have now in Hybris Commerce Suite 5.7 The following picture is from out of box, how many gradle recipes does hybris have. That’s not the whole list. As a hybris expert, we need to get our heads down and keep updating out skills I guess...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>YaaS! Hybris as a Service? What&#39;s that?</title>
	<link>http://www.kungfusoftware.net/posts/yass-brief-look</link>
	<guid>/posts/yass-brief-look</guid>
	
	<pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<description>SAP Hybris recently released YaaS Open Beta. Now every individual or organisation can register for free at the moment. (At least the time I am writing this post 09/10/2015) Overview and background YaaS stands for Hybris as a Service. So it’s really a big cloud offering from hybris in the...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Pow! Guess what the best Commerce Platform on the planet is?</title>
	<link>http://www.kungfusoftware.net/posts/hybris-best-ecommerce-platform</link>
	<guid>/posts/hybris-best-ecommerce-platform</guid>
	
	<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<description>Gartner recently released their Critical Capabilities for Digital Commerce report, where 11 vendors were evaluated on products based on five critical capabilities and three use cases. And it is good, really good. Hybris Commerce has been named the leader for each use case, making it the best Commerce platform in...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Ecommerce Solutions on the market</title>
	<link>http://www.kungfusoftware.net/posts/ecommerce-solutions-on-the-market</link>
	<guid>/posts/ecommerce-solutions-on-the-market</guid>
	
	<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<description>With the new Gartner Report for Digital Commerce, Gartner listed SAP hybris as the best Ecommerce Platform among other 10 ecommerce solutions. And pointed Hybris receives highest product scores in all 3 use cases. Click here to ask for a free report. I feel good because I have been working...</description>
</item><item>
	<title>Release Notes</title>
	<link>http://www.kungfusoftware.net/posts/release-notes</link>
	<guid>/posts/release-notes</guid>
	
	<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<description>V1.1.3 - 13 Nov 2015 fixing some typos add open source section V1.1.2 - 22 Jun 2015 add social sharing features bug fixes add new blog post V1.1.1 - 15 Jun 2015 add basic google analytics add author info sections bug fixes V1.1.0 - 10 Jun 2015 add domain kungfusoftware.net...</description>
</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
